go4hosting.com 2018-06-27

# Read Our Privacy Policy – Go4hosting

**ABOUT US**

Cyfuture India Pvt. Ltd. and our subsidiaries (“us” or “Cyfuture”) are leading providers of web hosting for small, medium and large businesses to build and establish the web presence efficiently as well as cater to the customers/clients successfully. Our brands include Go4hosting, DialWebHosting, ComputeHost, DataBagg, and CloudOYE which can be found at <https://www.cyfuture.com/ourbrands.html> . We at Cyfuture are concerned regarding personal information of the visitors and customers using our websites, apps, services or products. This privacy policy offers details how the personal info is shared, collected and utilized by us. In order to know more about us, visit: <https://www.cyfuture.com/>. In case, you have any queries regarding our privacy policy or practices mentioned herein, so you can contact Futuristic Internet Services LLC, 10685-B Hazelhurst Dr. # 15644, Houston, TX 77043, USA. 

**INFORMATION COVERED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

The privacy policy covers all personal information, such as collecting, sharing and using your information described below. It applies to certain domains of the Cyfuture family like Go4hosting, DialWebHosting, ComputeHost, DataBagg, and CloudOYE. It doesn’t covers how users might utilize or share data collected by them utilizing our services. 

When you buy services from us, your information will be utilized and shared with the privacy policy’ provisions provided by Cyfuture.

By providing your personal information to us in the ways described in this Privacy Policy, you:

  * agree that you are authorized to provide that information;
  * are accepting this Privacy Policy and any supplementary privacy statement that may be relevant to you.

If you do not agree to our practices, please do not register, subscribe, create an account, or otherwise interact with our services or Brands.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU**

In the usage of services, we collect below-mentioned information about you. We collect the data for purposes defined under “How We Use Your Information”. 

**LOG IN FOR USER INFORMATION AND SERVICES**

  * Information provided by you before registration process like your email 
  * Information provided by you while registration process, such as related to co-branded offer (like your name, phone number, company name, billing address, email address, geographic location, industry, and credit card info) when you email us or call us or the moment you utilize our services or products 
  * Payment info provided to us at the time of purchase of products/services, such as credit card data 

**WEBSITE VISITS, SUPPORT AND USE OF SERVICES**

  * Data related to online activity on the websites in respect to services include following things – 
    * IP Address
    * Geographic Location
    * Version and Browser type
    * Pages Views by You
    * How You Got our Services and links clicked by you to leaving our services
    * When information is updated by you, else you avail our new services
    * Metadata used by you and contacts’ use of the services and emails send by you
    * Interactions with the videos offered by us
    * Issues encountered by you needs our assistance or support
    * Any communication method or device used to do an interaction with services

We store all this data collected from different places within the infrastructure, such as back end databases, analytics systems and log files. 

**SOCIAL MEDIA**

  * Information from the third-party social networking websites like information provided to us by using the credentials at these websites (like name and email address in order to pre-populate the sign-up form). 
  * Information provided by you permit us to right to use and it varies according to social networking website, depending in privacy settings’ level you have at social networking website. You can find out more and control about the privacy settings at appropriate social networking website. 

**OTHER SOURCES**

  * Information provided by us at the seminars or to the partners 
  * Information provided by you in the surveys
  * Your publicly available information
  * Information approved by you which is received from third parties.

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

We have appropriate interest in efficiently running a business and offering useful content and services. We collect and utilize the information combined or on its own with other info collected about you for below-mentioned purposes –

  * To offer requests services or products to you
  * To provide useful content to you
  * To make sure proper services’ functioning
  * To offer request technical support or information
  * To facilitate movement through websites or utilize our services
  * To do great marketing and advertising job of our services (we utilize this information in order to do this with your accord needed by applicable law)
  * To market and advertise third-party services and products (like an advt. is performed with permission where consent is much needed by appropriate law)
  * To diagnose the problems with services or servers provided by us
  * To administrate our sites
  * To do a communication with you
  * To target customers with our services or products (like targeting is just performed with permission where consent is needed by appropriate law
  * To contribute us in providing tailored services or personalized experience to you

Also, we use information received by us in anonymized and aggregated formats in order to produce reports on the statistics and trends like email open rates by the industry, mobile search trends and best practices of campaign or users which need to be exposed, clicked on the websites or bought our products/services.

The payment information provided by you like credit card info will be utilized to simplify payment for the services and products.

**INFORMATION SHARING**

As mentioned below, we just share your personal info with –

  * Other members of Cyfuture family
  * For legal reasons
  * In connection with merger, corporate reorganization, acquisition or sale 

**SHARING WITHIN CYFUTURE FAMILY**

We share your personal information with cyfuture’s family in order to allow corporate affiliates to make your interaction with products, services or offers which might be of your interest and provides you services and products. Any corporate affiliate might use the information as per terms of the privacy policy. In case, you resides within the jurisdiction where sharing needs permission, so we will just do it with your agreement. 

**CORPORATE REORGANIZATIONS**

In case, we are tangled in an acquisition, merger, sale of all or a considerable portion of our assets, or similar sale transaction, your personal information will be moved as portion of transaction. We at Cyfuture will notify you through a prior notice or email on our website regarding any choice and transfer you might have about your information. 

**LEGAL PROCESS**

Finally, if it is legally needed or if we believe that the disclosure is necessary, we might disclose personal information provided by you to law enforcement authorities, courts of law and third parties like internet service providers in order to conduct information, then you need to respond to them or court order in bringing legal action and avoid harm when you or third party might be –

  * Causing harm or injury to legal rights like property, users, us or to third parties
  * Violating terms and conditions
  * Violation state, local, federal or any other applicable law 

It comes in our policy to inform you that we need to give your personal information to the third parties connected with summons. 

**SECURITY**

The information transmission through email, text message or internet is not entirely secure. Though, we will try our best in order to secure personal information; however, we can’t guarantee security if your information get transmitted via email or services. Any of the transmission will be at your own risk. When we receive your information, we take appropriate organizational and technical measures in order to safeguard the personal information against theft/unauthorized use, loss, modification or access. 

The time we gather financial account info like credit card numbers, we secure the transmission via encryption like TLS – Transport Layer Security protocol. 

**ONLINE ADVERTISING AND TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES**

We make use of web beacons, cookies, tags, pixels, scripts and similar technologies in our business. Info regarding the technologies used by us, why we utilize them (for instance, related to online advertising) and how these can be controlled, you can find all this information in our [Cookie Policy.](https://www.endurance.com/privacy/cookie-policy/)

## CHOICE/OPT-OUT

**MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS FROM US**  
**EMAIL**

Every time, you have an opportunity to opt out of our marketing communications or changing preferences by succeeding a footer’ link of all non-transactional email messages from our side. A few communications from our side are deliberated service or transactional communications (for instance, important billing information and account notifications), and your account(s) for Cyfuture are offered to you on the condition which you receive on these communications from us. In case, you don’t want to receive service or transactional communications, then you need to cancel your account (s) for Cyfuture services and products. To cancel your Cyfuture account, kindly follow instructions which can be found in service terms for applicable Cyfuture service. Still, you might get marketing communications from our side even post canceling account if you too opt-out of marketing communications provided by us as mentioned below –

**PHONE**

We might contact you via telephone, with your permission wherever applicable for marketing purposes (such as prerecorded message or automatic dialer). In case, you don’t wish to receive these marketing calls, you can contact to our customer support through which you purchase services. If, you don’t need to agree in order to receive these automated texts or marketing phone calls from our side. 

**COOKIES**

To know, how to opt out and manage from cookies, kindly visit our [Cookie Policy](https://www.endurance.com/privacy/cookie-policy/)

**INFORMATION FROM THIRD PARTIES**

In order to manage information received regarding you from third parties (in case applicable) or social networking website, so you need to follow instructions from the party in order to update your information and change privacy settings whenever available. Information collected by us is covered by privacy policy and info collected by third party is subjected to privacy practices of third party. The choices of privacy made by you on privacy practices of third party. These have to make on third party website won’t apply to our utilization of information collected directly via our services. 

**UNAUTHORIZED ACCOUNTS**

In case a profile or account was made without your authorization and knowledge, kindly contact the customer support of brand on which profile or account is situated to request removal of profile or account. 

## RETENTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We retain personal information in order to offer services and otherwise needed to comply with legal obligations and apply our agreements. We would retain your information for not over seven years following later of  
(i) the termination date of your use of services   
(ii) 1 June 2018, unless we are otherwise essential by regulation or law required to retain personal information for a longer duration.

**YOUR RIGHTS**

You have rights in relation to the personal information we hold about you. We set out below an outline of those rights and how to exercise those rights. Please note that we will require you to verify your identity before responding to any requests to exercise your rights by providing details only known to the account holder. To exercise any of your rights, kindly visit [Privacy Center](https://www.cyfuture.com/privacy.html). Please note that for each of the rights below we may have valid legal reasons to refuse your request, in such instances we will let you know if that is the case.

**ACCESS**

You have the right to know whether we process personal information about you, and if we do, to access data we hold about you and certain information about how we use it and who we share it with.

**PORTABILITY**

You have the right to receive a subset of the personal information you provide us if we process it on the legal bases of our contract with you or with your consent in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and a right to request that we transfer such personal information to another party. If you wish for us to transfer the personal information to another party, please ensure you detail that party and note that we can only do so where it is technically feasible. We are not responsible for the security of the personal information or its processing once received by the third party.

**CORRECTION**

You have the right to require us to correct any personal information held about you that is inaccurate and have incomplete data completed. Where you request correction, please explain in detail why you believe the personal information we hold about you to be inaccurate or incomplete so that we can assess whether a correction is required. Please note that while we assess whether the personal information we hold about you is inaccurate or incomplete, you might exercise your right to restrict our processing of the applicable data as described below.

**ERASURE**

You may request that we erase the personal information we hold about you in the following circumstances:

  * where you believe it is no longer necessary for us to hold the personal information;
  * we are processing it on the basis of your consent and you wish to withdraw your consent;
  * we are processing your data on the basis of our legitimate interest and you object to such processing;
  * You no longer wish us to use your data to send you marketing; or
  * You believe we are unlawfully processing your data.

Please provide as much detail as possible on your reasons for the request to assist us in determining whether you have a valid basis for erasure.

**RESTRICTION OF PROCESSING TO STORAGE ONLY**

You have a right to require us to stop processing the personal information we hold about you other than for storage purposes in the following circumstances:

  * You believe the personal information is not accurate for the period it takes for us to verify whether the data is accurate;
  * We wish to erase the personal information as the processing we are doing is unlawful but you want us to simply restrict the use of that data;
  * We no longer need the personal information for the purposes of the processing but you require us to retain the data for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims; or
  * You have objected to us processing personal information we hold about you on the basis of our legitimate interest and you wish us to stop processing the personal information while we determine whether there is an overriding interest in us retaining such personal information.

**OBJECTION**

You have the right to object to our processing of data about you and we will consider your request. Please provide us with detail as to your reasoning so that we can assess whether there is a compelling overriding interest in us continuing to process such data or we need to process it in relation to legal claims.

You also have the right, at any time, to object to our processing of data about you in order to send you marketing, including where we build profiles for such purposes and we will stop processing the data for that purpose.

**WITHDRAWAL OF CONSENT**

Where you have provided your consent to us processing your personal data, you can withdraw your consent anytime by visiting [Privacy Center](https://www.cyfuture.com/privacy.html). 

**INFORMATION COLLECTION, THIRD PARTY LINKS AND USE BY OUR USERS**

Some of our services provide links to other websites. Because we do not control the information policies or practices of these third party sites, you should review their privacy policies to learn about how they collect and use personal information.

You may also log in to some of our Services using sign-in services such as an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you with the option to share certain personal information with us, such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. For example, if you take advantage of certain of our social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, and widgets, such as the “Share This” button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site, the applicable social networking sites may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our websites, and may set a cookie to enable it to function properly.

**CHILDREN**

Our services are not directed to persons under 18. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personal information without such parent or guardian’s consent, he or she should contact us. If we become aware that a child under 18 has provided us with personal information, we will delete such information from our files.

**DATA TRANSFER**

In order for us to provide the services to you, your personal information will be transferred to, and stored at/processed in the United States. Your personal data is also processed by staff operating in India and UK. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your personal data is treated securely and in accordance with this policy.

For transfers of personal information within the Cyfuture family, such transfer will be under the Commission’s model contracts for the transfer of personal data to third countries (i.e., the standard contractual clauses), pursuant to Decision 2004/915/EC and 2010/87/EU.

For transfers of data to third parties, such transfers will either (i) be under the Commission’s model contracts for the transfer of personal data to third countries (i.e., the standard contractual clauses), pursuant to Decision 2004/915/EC and 2010/87/EU; or (ii) rely on the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework.

You can contact the Data Protection Officer listed below to obtain a copy of the data transfer agreement or more information regarding the relevant safeguard we put in place. For more information about the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework, please visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield website.

**NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we decide to change this privacy policy in any material way, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on https://www.cyfuture.com/ or the website of the Cyfuture product or service you use prior to the change becoming effective. In all cases, your continued use of any Services constitutes acceptance to any such changes.

If you want to work on privacy settings or want to give option to users, you can do the same. I found privacy settings of autodesk very interesting and relevant.
